This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
♫Always making that face whenever you see me♫
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
♫Always making that face whenever you see me♫
♫What does that mean?♫
[Present]
♫Whatever I say upset you, but you’ll get mad if I keep quiet♫
♫I really don’t know what to do♫
♫When deep down, I really like you♫
♫But you probably don’t care♫
♫Should I just say it out loud?♫
♫Or keep it all to myself and let it be?♫
♫What should I do?♫
♫I don’t know how to tell you how I feel♫
♫I’m still confused by the way you react when I’m around♫
♫I’m still afraid. Will it be all right if I say it?♫
♫So I have to hide it inside♫
♫I don’t know what to do with these feelings♫
♫Always keep dreaming of you, night after night♫
♫What should I do? I can’t just let it go on like this♫
♫But I’m too afraid to say it, so I’ll just keep it to myself♫
Flaming Chains of Love
[Previously]
My friend and her daughter are here to visit me, so I want to take them to see the cave in the mine.
But aren’t you afraid of the dark and narrow space, Miss Phrao?
Miss Panee did it on purpose.
My diamond ring is gone!
This is all your fault. You must go in there and find it.
Help!
Kaphrao!
Let’s hurry and get out of here.
The heavy rain has caused a landslide, Master.
This is all because of you!
Fai!
Get out of Fai’s life now!
- Aunt Nee!
- Get out!
Ak, your daughter is protecting your mistress’s child.
Kaphrao is the daughter of someone I’m indebted to. He died for me.
Your dad had sacrificed his life for my dad.
But I still let Aunt Nee hurt you.
You did protect me today.
Maybe we should make a horse stable on the edge of our farm, what do you think?
That’s great. And it’d be nice to have a duck farm too.
Ducks?
Din!
Miss you so much!
How’s the drive? Tired?
Not really.
Believe me?
No.
Hello.
- Hello.
Look, next time, try to plan beforehand where you’re going.
You’re lucky you called first. Otherwise, you would’ve gone north for nothing.
I didn’t expect we’d end up here too.
Who would’ve known you’d be here?
By the way, Din,
can I borrow your clothes? We didn’t get to stop by anywhere.
Sure. And if you need more, you can go buy new ones.
Kaphrao can borrow Rose’s clothes.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
As for your room, it’s already taken care of. It’s right next to mine.
I’ll take Miss Phrao to her room first, so she can freshen up and get changed.
I’ll leave her to you then, Boss Rose.
I need to talk to Din for a bit.
Don’t worry.
Let’s go then.
Come.
What’s up, kiddo?
Got a problem.
You only come to me when there’s a problem.
It’s bad.
Really?
You and Fai can stay in this room.
Can you two sleep in the same room?
Yes.
I’ll go bring you some clothes.
If you need anything, you can always let me know.
Thank you so much, Miss Rose.
What happened?
Just some sort of family conflict.
Do you want to tell me about it?
I’m always here to listen.
And that’s what happened.
So, I figured we shouldn’t go home now–don’t want to make it worse.
Just came here to catch our breath first.
You did the right thing. Staying there would only add fuel to the fire.
Aunt Nee is probably so mad at me right now.
Obviously, you went against her to protect Phrao like that.
Is this the first time you had a row with Aunt Panee?
So, have you realised now that you like her?
Yes, I like Phrao.
If she’s the one for you, then don’t ever let her go again.
We’re with Din now, Dad.
Please don’t worry.
Yes.
Please take care of Aunt Nee for me.
I’m a bit worried about Miss Panee though.
Whose number is this?
It’s Aunt Nee.
Don’t answer it.
But if you want to, just let me do the talking.
That would only make her more furious.
I’ll do it.
Then, put her on speaker so that I could help in case there’s anything.
Hello?
Where are you taking my niece?
What lies are you telling her to make her hate me?
You scumbag!
Ak didn’t fall for you so you’re going for my niece instead.
That’s enough, Aunt Nee.
Fai?
Is that you, dear?
What lies did that girl tell you?
Don’t listen to her.
You know how much I love you, don’t you?
I know.
And I love you too, Aunt Nee.
If you love me, then you should stay away from her, dear.
Aunt Nee.
You also hate her, don’t you?
Everything I did, I did it for you.
You’re the one who told me to find a way to get rid of her, remember?
Why are you mad at me now?
You have to be careful.
She’s nasty, you’re no match for her.
Get away from that filthy rat as fast as you can.
Hold on, Kaphrao. Listen to me first.
I can explain.
Save it. I’ve known since 15 years ago how much you hate me.
And now, I hate you a lot too!
Kaphrao!
Kaphrao, please listen to me. I can–
[♫Have you ever loved me? Please let me know…♫]
[♫If those hugs you gave me meant anything at all♫]
[♫I don’t want to imagine it alone. Do you also feel the same?♫]
You hate her too, don’t you?
♫Forget about that promise and tell me honestly♫
♫If you’ve ever loved me at all♫
I really don’t know why Aunt Nee said that.
Now, Kaphrao thinks that I hate her.
Your aunt probably knew you put her on speaker.
She said it on purpose so Phrao would hear it.
To drive a wedge between you two.
I should go tell her about this then.
Hey, not yet.
Give her some time.
You’d only make things worse if you do it now.
Maybe you should wait until tomorrow.
Just sleep in my room tonight.
Miss Phrao refuses to come out of her room.
I tried to order something for her to eat but she said she’s not hungry.
She also said she has a headache and isn’t feeling well.
A headache?
Hey, calm down.
What now?
She’s still upset.
Just give her time.
She’ll come out when she feels better.
She has to eat somehow.
You can try making it up to her then.
Really?
Yeah.
But I’ve never done anything like this before.
Din, help me.
Huh? Just like that?
Well, you were quite an expert when you tried to make Boss Rose forgive you.
Please help her, honey.
Pleaseee.
- Please help me, Sis.
- Yeah, please help her.
Please, Sis.
Just help her, honey.
Anything to make Kaphrao feel better and talk to me.
So that I can explain about everything and…
confess to her.
A love confession?
We have to create a romantic vibe.
Let’s start then, shall we?
How’s the food?
It’s amazing.
If you want to eat anything, just go ahead and order it.
Thank you but I don’t have much appetite today.
Rose, should we play charades after this?
There are many of us today, it should be fun.
That's brilliant.
Miss Phrao, please join us.
Well, I…
I…
Please.
We don’t often get to be together like this.
I’m so fed up playing it with Din alone.
Please, please, please.
Yes?
All right.
Riding a bike.
Sitting on a bike.
- No, but there’s a word ‘bike’.
- A biker.
It’s an occupation.
Motorbike taxi?
That was close!
Motorbike taxi driver!
- That’s right!
- No ‘driver’ though.
Jack and Rose.
Titanic!
What is it?
Do that again.
Mirroring?
A mirror?
- What is it?
- A ninja.
Dancing?
A lion dance!
Squirrel.
Belly?
Doraemon.
No, not that! How could this be Doraemon?
A kangaroo!
Correct!
Fish.
Chest fish. Heart fish. Er…
What is it?
Climbing Perch fish! *(Pla Moh or physician fish in Thai)
Correct.
Carp fish! (*Carp/Krub - a polite ending word used by male speakers)
That’s right!
- A couple?
- Lovers?
A fish?
Tuna?
Pisces? What is it?
I’m having a headache. Please excuse me then. I’m sorry.
[Patongko] (*Youtiao or Chinese crullers)
This is it. She’s in a good mood right now.
What are you waiting for?
Do you want to miss this chance?
But what if she–
Geez, you dork! Just go.
Go on.
Go!
Kaphrao.
What?
Can we talk?
Aren’t we talking now?
Not like that.
Why are you avoiding me?
I’m not. I’m standing right in front of you.
Just hurry up and get it over with.
Well, I…
I…
If you’re not going to say it, I will.
Going back this time, I’ll tell Uncle that I’m going to work in Bangkok.
I don’t want to cause your family any more trouble.
No, I won’t let you–
I’m not asking for your permission. I’m only letting you know.
About what Aunt Nee said, I can explain.
Honestly, I don’t hate you at all.
Then, how do you feel about me?
I…
Forget it. I don’t want to hear it anymore.
Kaphrao! Wait.
Don’t follow me.
You’re terrible.
If that’s the best you could do, don’t call me Boss anymore.
A great humiliation to the Watinwanich family.
But Kaphrao is…
She’s what?
Why can’t you just speak your mind like when you insulted her?
I’m just afraid she might hate me even more if I say it.
But she already hates you anyway, doesn’t she?
If it were me, I’d just say it. I don’t want to regret it later.
How should I confess to her then?
I’ve never done it before.
Don’t worry. Leave that to the boss.
It’s so nice and calm here.
Din and I are planning to build a resort in Chiang Rai.
So, we came here in case we might be able to get some ideas.
Please don’t forget to invite me once it’s done. I really want to see it.
How could I forget? You’ll soon become a part of our family.
Was that supposed to be a joke, Miss Rose?
Just kidding.
But I’ll definitely invite you.
Yes, honey?
Okay, sure. At the reception? I’ll be there shortly.
I’ll be right back, Miss Phrao.
Din just ran into the owner of this place, so she wants to introduce me to them.
Please take your time.
Okay.
Kaphrao.
Hold on, listen to me first.
About what Aunt Nee said, I admit I used to say that.
But it was long ago when I was still a kid. I actually don’t hate you.
I want to apologise for everything I’ve done.
I was wrong.
Never mind, it’s all in the past.
What?
As an apology.
Hey, I made it myself.
You know I’ve never done this for anyone.
Fine.
I just don't want it to go to waste.
I’m also sorry for saying I hate you earlier.
Then…
Now that we’ve cleared it up, don’t forget to say thank you to Miss Rose.
So, you knew?
Hold on.
There’s still one more thing.
What now?
It’s about your Phi Jah.
I might come later but I’m definitely not going to back down.
Seriously, Fai, can we stop talking about that?
Fine, I’m going to say it my way then.
Kaphrao.
I like you.
I’ve liked you for a long time.
You don’t have to answer me now. I can wait.
♫What should I do? I can’t just let it go on like this♫
♫But I’m too afraid to say it, so I’ll just keep it to myself♫
♫I’ll just keep it to myself♫
So, does she like me or not?
I’m going crazy!
[Fai]: Kaphrao.
I like you.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
I’ve liked you for a long time.
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
You don’t have to answer me now. I can wait.
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
Can’t sleep?
Yeah, you too?
Well, I…
I won’t bother you then.
Hold on.
Please stay and talk to me first.
Are you still mad at me because I said I like–
No!
So, do you hate me?
No, I don’t.
Why? Or do you want me to hate you?
I’m just afraid you might hate me because I told you how I feel.
About what you said, are you sure about it?
I am!
But we’ve never had a good time together.
We’ve always been fighting. How could you possibly like me?
I don’t believe you.
But for me, I like every moment I spend with you.
How about we go to the mountain together?
To create our own happy moments.
I’m not sure if Miss Din and Miss Rose are free though.
It can just be the two of us.
If they’re also coming, how could we call it a date?
Whatever. It’s either two of us alone,
or else I’m not going.
Don’t you want to go there with me?
Of course, I do–so much too.
♫ You’re the one that change my life ♫
♫ Make me feel more important than anyone♫
♫ Thank you so much♫
♫ For making my life meaningful♫
♫ How lucky I am to have you♫
Thank you.
Aww, there’re three of us here but you only top it up for her alone.
How very caring of you.
Come on. It’s me, your little sister.
Yesterday at the creak, how was it, Miss Phrao?
At the creak?
It was fine. Good.
Really good.
Boss Rose.
What about last night? Was it good, Fai?
Last night? Sure, it was great.
Aren’t you eating?
Little Fireball, don’t you have anything to share with your sisters?
Nope.
Nothing at all.
By the way, Din–
The mountain, right? I already booked a tent for you.
Miss Phrao,
please do enjoy your moments there.
Stargazing at night and waking up to the sea of fog in the morning.
How romantic–an absolutely perfect place for a date.
Not a date, Miss Rose.
It’s hanging out. We’d just go hanging out there.
- Hanging out?
- Yes.
Yeah, hanging out.
That’s right.
Yeah.
Just hanging out and looking around.
Looking around for love?
We’re going camping. Didn’t you already book a tent for us?
Oh, that’s right. I did book it for you.
The weather there is quite cold, you might want to sleep in each other’s arms.
Boss Rose!
Hugging.
Stop talking nonsense.
Isn’t the food nice? Have some more then.
Here you go, my dear sis.
Thanks.
So full of happiness, huh?
It’s spilling out of my ears.
What are you thinking?
I’m thinking about what I’ll have to face when I go home.
Later then.
For now, you should just let it go. Relax and recharge yourself
so that you can fight the problem later.
Do you really believe I could fix it?
There’s always a solution to every problem.
Just never let go of each other’s hand.
I still don’t know if she wants to hold my hand.
She has never even said she likes me.
Ever since I can remember, the Young Master that I know has never given on anything so easily.
How come you’re so quick to give up when it comes to love?
Are you really Fai?
Well,
if I were kind like you,
calm like Nam, and sweet like Lom;
maybe Kaphrao would like me more.
Listen, you don’t need to try to be like anyone.
Just be a better version of yourself, and that’s enough.
If she’s going to like you, I’m sure she’ll like you as you are.
Trust me.
Geez, you’re so down bad for her.
Are you Fai for real?
Of course.
Then how come you’re acting like a lovesick fool?
It’s done.
We should get the best view from this spot.
Where’s the other tent?
I only brought one.
What? Why did you only bring one?
The tent is huge. There’s plenty of room for two people. Look.
Are you scared?
I’m not going to do anything to you.
I just want to hang out with you, not to do that kind of thing.
Try it and you’re dead.
Ooh, I’m so scared.
Hey, can you help me set up the chair and table?
No, just do it yourself.
I’ll go look around.
Please, Phrao. Please help me.
So that we could go for a walk together after this.
Fine, I’ll help. But only because there’re just two of us here.
Not that I’d want to go for a walk with you.
Where should I put it?
Over there. Come.
Sit down.
The view is really nice.
Miss Rose said the stars here look so beautiful at night.
Do you think we’ll see them tonight?
Maybe or maybe not–it doesn’t matter though.
We can come back anytime.
From now on, can you call me ‘Phi’ (Big Sis) like when we were young?
I’m going to call myself ‘Phi’ when I talk to you too.
Why?
I don’t want us to sound so distant.
If I can’t be your lover, at least I can still be your sister.
This is so weird. Are you someone else in disguise?
I’m trying to be a better person here.
Wouldn’t it be nice if I were as good as Din, Nam, or Lom?
When I was little, I was always compared to them.
I’ve never made my dad proud.
So, I don’t know if you’d see anything good in me or even like me at all.
When you like someone, it isn’t because they remind you of someone else.
You like them as who they are.
So, do you like me, Phrao?
I’ll be back.
Hold on.
I don’t want to make you feel uncomfortable.
So silly.
I was quiet because I’m still thinking.
But before I say it, can I ask you one thing?
Go ahead.
That day, 15 years ago,
did you do that because you wanted me to disappear from your life forever?
If I get first place in class, I’ll ask Uncle to buy me this plushie.
Isn’t it cute?
Do you really think someone like you could ever make it that far?
This way.
Put it in there.
Uncle!
Yes, dear?
What is it?
My exam result.
Your exam result? Let me see.
Wow! You passed all subjects. That’s brilliant, my girl.
You deserve a reward then. How about an ice-cream?
Do you like it?
Well done!
Fai, try to study like your sister.
Understood?
Come, let me see it again.
What flavour do you want?
Chocolate.
Chocolate?
Should we go this evening then?
Chocolate.
I can buy you a gift even if you didn’t get first place, dear.
Here we are. This shop, isn’t it?
Yes.
Go on and pick one then.
You want this one?
Yes.
You said you’d trust me. If you chicken out, then let’s not play.
Fine, I’ll do it.
Get in there then.
1, 2, 3…
Slowly.
4,5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11…
Uncle.
Yes?
Where’s the truck that was here earlier?
It just left a while ago, Young Master.
That day, I actually went back to get a plushie to surprise you.
I know it sounds like an excuse to you.
So, you’ve never wanted me to disappear from your life.
No.
I’m sorry.
If I could turn back time, I wouldn’t have done that to you.
Just knowing that you don’t hate me is more than enough.
I don’t hate you.
I like you.
You should look at me when you say that.
Are you teasing me?
You used to tease me a lot. It’s my turn now.
Phi Jah.
So mean! Why calling someone else's name while hugging me?
Stop being so silly, Phi Jah.
Hang on.
Phi Jah?
Did you mean me?
Of course, it’s you.
Really?
So, you’ve always liked me?
If you still don’t get it, I don’t know what to say anymore.
Phi Jah, you’re the luckiest girl in the world!
Hey, keep your voice down!
Phrao!
♫I don’t know how to tell you how I feel♫
♫I’m still confused by the way you react when I’m around♫
My dear Phrao.
I’m so happy.
♫I’m still confused by the way you react when I’m around♫
♫I’m still afraid. Will it be all right if I say it?♫
Took you long enough.
♫So I have to hide it inside♫
♫I don’t know what to do with these feelings♫
I almost died from stressing out.
I want you to figure it out for yourself.
♫Always keep dreaming of you, night after night♫
I’m so happy that I’m your Phi Jah.
♫What should I do? I can’t just let it go on like this♫
♫But I’m too afraid to say it, so I’ll just keep it to myself♫
Phi Jah, Phi Jah, Phi Jah, Phi Jah!
♫I’ll just keep it to myself♫
How could I sleep if you keep staring at me like that?
I’m afraid you’ll disappear if I close my eyes and open them again.
Where would I be then? I’m right next to you now.
You’re right.
Are you cold?
Is it better?
Can you move a little closer to me?
Closer.
So warm.
The blanket can also keep you warm.
Why do you need to hug me?
Do you find it annoying?
When we were young, yes.
But not anymore.
Does that mean you knew I secretly snuggled close to you?
I’ve known all along.
But you don’t need to do it secretly anymore.
You have my permission now.
Are you shy?
Sleep now. Or else I’ll throw you out of the tent.
Try it if you dare.
No, I don’t.
I won this time, Phi Jah.
You’ve always won.
I’ve just never let you know until now.
Going back this time, I’m not going to let anyone hurt you again.
Aunt Nee would probably do anything to break us apart.
But I’ll never let go of your hand.
I promise I’ll protect you as best as I can.
I promise that no matter what happens,
I’ll never let go of your hand too.
Phrao.
Wake up, baby. We’re home now.
Why did you bring me here? Why didn’t you drop me off at the worker’s lodge first?
I told Dad we’d be here.
That I’d introduce my girlfriend to him.
Phi Jah!
Are you sure? Isn’t it too soon?
Dad is also your guardian. I should do it the proper way.
Remember what I told you, that I’ll never let Dad take you in as another daughter.
I’d only allow you to be his daughter-in-law.
I’m not going.
You’re always like this.
Take me back to the worker’s lodge.
No.
Ready?
Kaphrao and I are together now.
We just want to let you know that we’re seeing each other.
That’s good.
I’m happy for you.
That’s it? You’re not gonna scold me?
For what?
It’s your happiness.
Why would I disagree?
Well, because I’m not a good girl.
So, you might think I don’t deserve to be with her.
Who told you that?
I might not be a gentle parent to you,
but I still know you well enough–
that you’re far from being a bad person.
On the other hand, no matter what people say about you,
I’ve always loved and been proud of you.
Dad.
Also,
I’ve always loved and cared for Kaphrao as if she were my own daughter.
But from now on, she’s no longer your daughter.
Huh? What would she be then?
Your daughter-in-law.
Fai!
What are you saying? I haven’t agreed to it yet.
Uncle, please don’t listen to her. She always loves to tease me.
Eh, what uncle? Call me ‘Dad’, dear.
Dad.
She already approved.
Not uncle.
Uncle.
It’s ‘Dad’.
Dad.
About moving into this house, can I just stay at the worker’s lodge like before?
I don’t want to cause any trouble.
But–
Don’t worry, I’ll look after her.
If she moves in now, I’m afraid Aunt Nee might…
I understand.
I’m also worried about that.
If your aunt knows about this, she might have made another ruckus.
But I have to tell her somehow.
I’ve been avoiding it all this time.
But I’m not going to run anymore.
I promise to protect her.
No matter what happens, I’ll always be by her side.
I respect both of your decisions.
And remember, girls–
no matter what happens–
I will always stand by you.
Remember that.
Dad!
I thought you already forgot I’m still here.
I’m sorry.
Where have you been?
It must have been fun since you’ve left me here for so many days.
I just went to see Din. As for Kaphrao–
Stop going anywhere with that girl. That’s an order!
I don’t get it. Why do you hate her so much?
Because she tries to seduce you!
She’s playing with your heart. You’re too naive to see it.
But I’m all grown up now.
I can tell what’s what.
Are you talking back to me?
Since you’ve been with that girl,
you’ve become so arrogant–not a sweet girl like you used to be.
Aunt Nee, Kaphrao and I, we–
I don’t care!
If you choose me, there’s no her.
Morning.
Phi Jah!
Fai, what are you doing here so early?
Here, your breakfast. Eat up so you’ll have energy to work.
Ahem!
Aww.
You two are so sweet it’s giving me diabetes just by looking.
Aren’t you heading off to work? Hurry up then.
Yes.
Look,
the other day you were still the Master’s adopted daughter.
But now you’re his daughter-in-law.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
Bua!
Just hurry out to work. And make sure your lips are sealed.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
Go now.
Okay.
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
I’m leaving. I love my job, I love my job!
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
This fried chicken is the best in town. It’s so delicious.
Aww, thank you.
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
Enjoy, you two.
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
Bua!
Bye!
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
Such a tease.
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
How long are you going to keep staring at my face?
I’m just admiring my own girlfriend. Can’t I do that?
[North Star Entertainment]
[Flaming Chains of Love]
I’m sorry. I still couldn’t find a chance to tell Aunt Nee about us.
I want to talk to you about that too.
About what?
It’s just…can we not tell other people about us yet?
I don’t want any more trouble.
Especially with your aunt.
But I already promise I’ll protect you.
Please give me some time. Pleaseee, Phi Jah.
Let’s wait until the situation clears up.
Please, pleaseee.
Okay, fine.
Is that all?
There’s more.
In front of other people, you must treat me like before.
Before? How?
Like those times when we could hardly stand each other.
You want me to pretend to hate you?
Please.
Can you do it for me, Phi Jah?
Please?
Just putting on an act to fool other people for a bit.
This much, only this much.
Please, pleaseee.
All right, all right.
But only when we’re in front of other people.
Yes.
You’re the sweetest, Phi Jah!
Do you love me then?
You’re getting bolder.
I’m going to eat.
Answer me first.
- Eat first.
- Tell me first.
- No, eat first.
- Do you love me?
Not telling you.
Then, I won’t eat.
Come on, Fai.
Do you love me?
Phi Jah, you already know how I feel. Hurry and eat your breakfast.
No, I don’t!
These are all the works you were supposed to do while you were away.
Get them done by today so other people won’t have to wait for you only.
But that’s a lot there.
So? You need to finish them anyway.
Or do you want me to tell Young Master?
Is that all?
I thought there’s more.
Just give her some reprimand, Young Master.
Quit slacking off and work faster!
And who told you to dump all the works on Athittaya?
Well, I just want to help you lighten the workload.
All of you, listen carefully.
From now on, if anyone wants to assign work to my assistant, you must get my approval first.
Understood?
Yes, Miss.
As for you, you need to be responsible for your mistakes.
Follow me to my office right now!
Hey, did you see her face?
As if she saw a ghost, right?
There, there. It’s all right, my baby.
How dare Duangnate try to bully my girlfriend like that?
Should I just cut down her pay?
Who do you think told her to bully me?
Me.
Phi Jah is nasty! Phi Jah is a bad girl!
Phi Jah caused you trouble…
Aww, you were so scary back there.
Let’s go eat with Dad at the main house this evening.
Don’t you have to go eat with your aunt?
I’m staying at the main house for now.
Auntie’s house hasn't been quite welcoming lately.
I’m so sorry I’ve caused you trouble.
I don’t want you and Aunt Nee–
It’s not your fault at all.
I can handle it.
All I need is for you to always be by my side.
But I’m feeling so drained right now.
Can you cheer me up a bit?
You can do it!
Nooo, not like that.
How do you want it?
Ahh, so sweet.
Phi Jah, don’t do that! We’re in the office!
Did you just hit me? I’ll punish you then.
Stop it. I’m going back to work.
Are you embarrassed, huh?
Do you still know the way back to your desk?
Want me to walk you there?
I’m not embarrassed.
Holy shit!
I’m sorry. I didn’t see anything.
I didn’t see you and Miss Phrao kissing.
We weren’t kissing!
I swear I won’t tell anyone.
Come on, Phrao.
I don’t want to work there anymore. I want to quit!
I’m sorry. I forgot to lock the door.
Stop it.
Listen, if you want to quit, then go ahead.
I can take care of you.
Phi Jah, stop joking around! What if your aunt hears about this?
She hasn’t heard about it yet.
You nasty bitch!
Phi Jah!
Fai…
Get out the way, dear. Move!
Out of the way! Move, Fai! Let me go!
No!
How dare you try to seduce my niece even at work?
No one is doing that.
Are you defending her?
When will you stop being so obsessed?
I’m not obsessed.
And I don’t hate her like how you’ve always wanted me to.
How dare you talk to me like that?
You know how much I hate her!
But I love her!
I love Phrao.
I’ve loved her all along.
Aunt Nee!
Phrao, call an ambulance!
Wake up, Aunt Nee!
Aunt Nee!
[Next Episode]
Phi Jah, if you ever have to choose, please choose Miss Panee.
I’m not going to choose anyone.
But what if one day, you have to make a choice.
Get her out of my face.
Aunt Nee.
I said get out!
Are you going to leave me for someone who’s just come into your life?
The doctor suggests we should separate her from whatever that arouses her to be like this.
And that’s Kaphrao.